<research>
<project id="BEESTARTNODE">
<name>Bees And Magic</name>
<popupText>Across Fields and Forest</popupText>
<longText>There is something about your world that makes you think trees and bees require more research.</longText>
<page type="text">A recent breakthrough has given you information regarding Apiculture and Arborculture. Perhaps it isn't quite as mundane as it first seemed.

The potential exists for further study. All that is required is some creative thinking to apply new uses to old, familiar items.</page>
</project>

<project id="FERTILIZER">
<name>Concentrated Compound</name>
<popupText>An Apatite for more...</popupText>
<longText>You believe you can extend your reserves of apatite by enriching the crafted material with something that crops may appreciate.</longText>
<page type="text">You have discovered a method to stretch your reserves of apatite to the limit through the use of magic. By infusing the mixture created by crushing the apatite crystals with dirt with the aspect of the Harvest, you can create additional reserves of it. This mixture is then diluted with sand to produce the normal variety of fertilizer.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FERTILIZER</page>
</project>

<project id="HIVEFRAME">
<name>Magic Frame</name>
<popupText>A Different Frame of Bee</popupText>
<longText>Continuing from your curiousity into these flying creatures, an idea has ocurred to you how to encourage them to work faster, coaxed along by the judicious use of magic applied to some existing beekeeping equipment.</longText>
<page type="text">The simple frames known to all beekeepers, while effective, are flimsy and prone to breakage. With the help of magic, you have devised an improved design to function longer by enchanting it with reinforcing magic.

These improved versions can last several times longer than the basic frames, thanks to your new enchantments.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FRAMEMAGIC</page>
</project>

<project id="HIVEFRAME2">
<name>Resilient Frame</name>
<popupText>Making it better...</popupText>
<longText>Having come up with an idea for an improved Magical Frame, the next logical step would be to reinforce the design further, shielding it from all but the harshest wear and tear. The trade-off, of course, would be an increased consumption of aura during its operation.</longText>
<page type="text">You have successfully created a design for a more durable Apiary Frame, the Resilient Frame. Like the Magic Frame, it will increase the bees' working speed and consume aura to offset received wear and tear. Unlike the Magic Frame, its expected lifespan is much longer. </page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FRAMERESILIENT</page>
</project>

<project id="HIVEFRAMEGENTLE">
<name>Gentle Frame</name>
<popupText>You won't even notice I'm here.</popupText>
<longText>Continuing from your curiosity into these flying creatures, an idea has occured to you how to encourage them to live slightly longer within the Apiaries. Perhaps if you could surround them with the essence of health, life, and the plants they love, you can realize this idea.</longText>
<page type="text">The Gentle Frame extends the life expectancy of a working queen by roughly a half, and encourages the workers to move at a slightly increased pace. The end result is that the bees live longer, and produce more while they are alive.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FRAMEGENTLE</page>
</project>

<project id="HIVEFRAMEMETA">
<name>Metabolic Frame</name>
<popupText>And One! And Two!</popupText>
<longText>Additional bee research has yielded insight into their body structure, metabolism, and life cycle. It is possible that you could create a frame to enhance their body processes.</longText>
<page type="text">The Metabolic Frame enhances the rate at which bees metabolize food, resulting in a higher work speed. However, this makes their genetic structure somewhat unstable and prone to mutations. While this can be frustrating for some apiarists, other, more prepared beekeepers have been known to use the Metabolic Frames in their apiaries to encourage mutations in bee species.

It is rather less durable than the Magic Frame.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FRAMEMETABOLIC</page>
</project>

<project id="HIVEFRAMENECRO">
<name>Necrotic Frame</name>
<popupText>Doom And Gloom, For Bees!</popupText>
<longText>After being stung by a bee, you concocted an idea to make them pay. Surely placing a frame infused with death and envenomed intents in a hive will teach them a lesson!</longText>
<page type="text">Your vengeance-fuelled research has paid off, resulting in the knowledge of the Necrotic Frame. This frame, when placed in an Apiary, will cause the bees to become sluggish, reducing their work speed, and severely unhealthy, greatly diminishing the current generation's lifespan. However, it is prudent to ensure the enchantments in the frame only affect the current generation.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FRAMENECROTIC</page>
</project>

<project id="HIVEFRAMETIME">
<name>Temporal Frame</name>
<popupText>Why isn't it blue and boxy?</popupText>
<longText>You have been seeking a way to significantly extend bee life. It should be possible by adding a frame enchanted with the essence of time to the hive.</longText>
<page type="text">Keeping bees has been frustrating, as the insects' short lives requires you to manually intervene far too often.

A new variation of your frame design, this version involving some Time magic, should help extend their lives significantly.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">FRAMETIME</page>
</project>

<project id="VOIDCAPSULE">
<name>Void Capsule</name>
<popupText>Another Dimension of Liquid Storage</popupText>
<longText>It seems reasonable that if you can shift blocks and other matter into an alternate dimension temporarily, you should be able to do something similar with liquids.</longText>
<page type="text">These new capsules can hold the equivalent of 8 buckets' worth of liquid by syphoning off a large quantity into a pocket dimension temporarily.

Like other capsules, they are fragile and are typically single-use. They have proven popular for long-term storage.</page>
<page type="infusioncrafting">VOIDCAPSULE</page>
</project>

<project id="THAUMIUMSCOOP">
<name>Thaumium Scoop</name>
<popupText>Stronger, Faster, Bee-ter</popupText>
<longText>It is possible to improve the durability of the scoop by creating them out of sterner materials. While you're at it, it may be helpful to enable them to be enchanted with restorative magics.</longText>
<page type="text">This improved scoop is more durable than the plain one your non-magical beekeeping friends are liable to use. It is good for three times as long as the average scoop at the cost of using some thaumium instead.

Because the thaumium present in its construction, it is possible to enchant the scoop with a Repairing spell in the usual manner.</page>
<page type="arcanecrafting">THAUMIUMSCOOP</page>
</project>

<project id="THAUMIUMGRAFTER">
<name>Thaumium Grafter</name>
<popupText>The Treesnipper</popupText>
<longText>This improved grafter is more durable than the plain one your non-magical arborist acquaintances tend to use in their exploits. It should be possible to allow them to be enchanted with repairing magic to make them last indefinitely.</longText>
<page type="text">Adding Thaumium to your grafter design has increased its durability significantly - up to two times longer than regular grafters.

It is also possible to enchant them with the Repair enchant, given sufficient experience. Using it rapidly may, however, give you a severe case of the munchies.</page>
<page type="arcanecrafting">THAUMIUMGRAFTER</page>
</project>

</research>